The Gilbert and Lila Silverman Fluxus Collection Archives
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series VI: Fluxhouse Cooperatives, 1965-1986
  - Subseries VI.B: Various
    - Material assembled for Silverman publication, undated; Original documents (including building plans, notes by Maciunas) with photocopies and notes assembled for unrealized publication planned by the Silverman Collection. This material was removed from a binder in order by the archivist and placed here. (Box 189, Folder VI.B.42)
    - "Medicaid", 1969; Forms. (Box 189, Folder VI.B.43)
    - "Misc. bills", 1974; Includes bills for classified ads in the Village Voice. (Box 189, Folder VI.B.44)
    - "Misc. plans, diagrams. / schedules", undated; Includes design for stainless steel kitchen sink. (Box 189, Folder VI.B.45)
    - New Marlborough, 1977, undated; Photographs, slides, negatives and contacts of the farm at New Marlborough, MA. (Box 189, Folder VI.B.46)
    - New Marlborough, 1985, undated; Photographs of the farm at New Marlborough, MA produced by the collection from Maciunas's negatives. Silverman #s:>483.Ia-hh Inventory #s: 02453 (Box 189, Folder VI.B.47)
    - New Marlborough, 1977, undated; Includes maps and photographs of George Maciunas at New Marlborough. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.48)
    - New Marlborough, undated; Large photographs of the farm at New Marlborough, MA produced by the collection from Maciunas's negatives. (Box 411, Folder VI.B.49*)
    - "Newsletters - originals", undated; Empty folder. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.50)
    - Newsletters and documents, undated; Newsletters; bulletins; schedule of deposits; various documents. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.51)
    - Newsletters and documents, 1966-1968, undated; Loft Building and Fluxhouse newsletters. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.52)
    - Newsletters and documents, 1967-1968, undated; Includes "Joko Juke Joint Preliminary Plan," "Plan for an Artist Condominium in New York City," "Fluxhouse Newsletter, 465 West Broadway Coop" (6/22/1968), "Fluxhouse Newsletter no. 10" (2/8/1967), "Information Bulletin on Fluxhouse Cooperatives," "Schedule of Deposits," photograph of 16 Greene st. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.53)
    - Notes and timesheets, 1976, undated (Box 190, Folder VI.B.54)
    - Occupants, undated; List of occupants for 131 Prince, 465 West Broadway, and 451 West Broadway. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.55)
    - "Other new bldgs. / 62 Greene", 1974, undated; File for buildings considered for purchase. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.56)
    - "Pop documents", 1977; Relates to purchase of farm at New Marlborough. Checks, including to Nijole Valaitis; ALS Nijole Valaitis - Maciunas (4/12/1977). Note: folder title appears not to be Maciunas's. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.57)
    - "Power of Attorney", 1974 (Box 190, Folder VI.B.58)
    - "Prop. lease - original & copy", undated; Lease. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.59)
    - "Recent bills - paid", 1974-1975; Map of Ville des Andelys; bills. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.60)
    - Sale offers and building plans, undated (Box 190, Folder VI.B.61)
    - "Signed bldg. applic.", undated; Department of Buildings work applications. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.62)
    - Stationery, undated; "Fluxhouse cooperative 1, 2 & 3 incorporated" stationery. Purchased from Backworks. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.63)
    - Taxes and bills, 1968-1975 (Box 190, Folder VI.B.64)
    - Time sheets, [1968]; 1 of 2 folders. Records of work done by various individuals. (Box 190, Folder VI.B.65)
    - Time sheets, [1968]; 2 of 2 folders. Records of work done by various individuals. (Box 191, Folder VI.B.66)
    - Various, 1967, undated; Includes legal documents; accounting; news clipping regarding planned downtown expressway (3/28/1967); notes. (Box 191, Folder VI.B.67)
    - Various, 1967-1968; From a folder labeled "misc. to be sorted" by Hendricks. Includes accounting, agreements, newsletters and bills. (Box 191, Folder VI.B.68)
    - Various plans and notes, undated (Box 191, Folder VI.B.69)
    - Violations, 1968-1970 (Box 191, Folder VI.B.70)
    - "Weprin / tax reassessment", 1971; Regards application of reassessment for Fluxhouse buildings. (Box 191, Folder VI.B.71)
    - "Work schedules", undated; 1 large fold-out calendar. (Box 191, Folder VI.B.72)
    - "Workmens compensation", 1968; Forms. (Box 191, Folder VI.B.73)
  - Subseries VI.C: Accounting
    These files appear to be Maciunas's own and may or may not reflect his original order.
    - "Time Sheets - blanks", undated (Box 191, Folder VI.C.1)
    - Stock certificates, 1969; Includes depositor's agreement. (Box 191, Folder VI.C.2)
    - "Recent Accounting", 1967-1968, undated (Box 191, Folder VI.C.3)
    - "Damone - bills", Bills and accounting for electrical contractor. (Box 191, Folder VI.C.4)
    - "Bills due - co-op", 1968-1969 (Box 191, Folder VI.C.5)
    - "Time-sheets - past", 1969, undated (Box 191, Folder VI.C.6)
    - "Canal lumber - Implosions / Dykes lumber", 1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.7)
    - "Electric - supplies", 1967-1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.8)
    - "Plumbling - supplies", 1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.9)
    - "Plumbing", 1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.10)
    - "Carpentry", 1967; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.11)
    - "Masonry", 1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.12)
    - "Lumber", 1967; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.13)
    - "Plumbing - work", 1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.14)
    - "Electric - contract", 1967; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.15)
    - "Boiler - heating", 1967; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.16)
    - "Zoning, permits, legal", 1967 (Box 192, Folder VI.C.17)
    - "Legal - papers & bills", 1966-1968 (Box 192, Folder VI.C.18)
    - "Workers", 1968; Accounting. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.19)
    - "Personal histories", undated; Biographies of artists; statement signed by artists in support of artists' cooperative housing. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.20)
    - "Mortgage & Tax", 1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.21)
    - "Vill. Voice", 1968; Receipts (for classified ads). (Box 192, Folder VI.C.22)
    - "Dantonas / Signature Lightning Ltd.", 1971; Financial information. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.23)
    - "Work schedules - past / Rules - instructions - Workers - refs.", undated (Box 192, Folder VI.C.24)
    - "Hardware", 1967-1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.25)
    - "Elevator", 1967-1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.26)
    - "Insurance", 1967-1968 (Box 192, Folder VI.C.27)
    - "Misc.", 1967-1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.28)
    - "Painting", 1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.29)
    - "Roof - skylights / Glazing - windows", 1968; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.30)
    - "Welding - cutting", 1967; Bills. (Box 192, Folder VI.C.31)
    - "Utilities - oil", 1968; Bills. (Box 193, Folder VI.C.32)
    - "Utilities", 1967-1968; Bills. (Box 193, Folder VI.C.33)
    - "Greene St. bills", 1967; Bills. (Box 193, Folder VI.C.34)
    - "Work schedules - blanks & past", undated; Bills. (Box 193, Folder VI.C.35)
    - "Bank statements / Checks", 1967; Accounting. (Box 193, Folder VI.C.36)
    - "Court - summonses", 1968 (Box 193, Folder VI.C.37)
    - "Corporation forms / filing receipts", 1968 (Box 193, Folder VI.C.38)
    - "Sale offers", undated; Includes plans and maintenance estimates for 16-18 Greene st. and 349 West Broadway. (Box 193, Folder VI.C.39)
    - "Taxes, Fees.", 1968 (Box 193, Folder VI.C.40)
    - "Legal fees", 1968 (Box 193, Folder VI.C.41)
    - "Medical bills", 1968; Workman's compensation. (Box 193, Folder VI.C.42)
    - "Loans", 1967 (Box 193, Folder VI.C.43)
    - "Tiles + Floor", 1967; Bills. (Box 193, Folder VI.C.44)
    - "Bldg. permits etc.", 1967 (Box 193, Folder VI.C.45)
    - "Rubbish - removal", 1967-1968; Bills. (Box 193, Folder VI.C.46)
  - Subseries VI.D: Bills, Business and Junk Mail
    This correspondence, some of which was sent to Maciunas after his death, is largely unopened. It was organized by Hendricks alphabetically by sender. It was considered Fluxhouse material, instead of general Maciunas files, by Hendricks because much of it regards Fluxhouse expenses. This correspondence was maintained because Hendricks considers it an important document of Maciunas's business activities. Select materials may be opened upon request.
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1980 (Box 193, Folder VI.D.1)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1982 (Box 193, Folder VI.D.2)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1980 (Box 194, Folder VI.D.3)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1975 (Box 194, Folder VI.D.4)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1981 (Box 194, Folder VI.D.5)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1968-1972 (Box 194, Folder VI.D.6)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1975 (Box 194, Folder VI.D.7)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1974-1975 (Box 195, Folder VI.D.8)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1979 (Box 195, Folder VI.D.9)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1971 (Box 195, Folder VI.D.10)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1975 (Box 195, Folder VI.D.11)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1981 (Box 195, Folder VI.D.12)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1975 (Box 196, Folder VI.D.13)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1981; Unsorted. (Box 196, Folder VI.D.14)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1981; Unsorted. (Box 196, Folder VI.D.15)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1981; Unsorted. (Box 196, Folder VI.D.16)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1981; Unsorted. (Box 196, Folder VI.D.17)
    - Bills, business and junk mail, 1970-1981; Unsorted. (Box 196, Folder VI.D.18)
- Series VII: Silverman Administrative Files, 1974-2010
  - Subseries VII.A: General Administrative Files
    These consist primarily of an alphabetical run created by Hendricks. Comprised mostly of correspondence to Hendricks or Silverman (and copies of outgoing correspondence), files are generally arranged by name of correspondent, but also hold research, notes, press clippings, photographs of individuals and works, and ephemera. Subjects are generally artists, scholars, museums, galleries, and book sellers, and pertain mostly to acquisitions, exhibitions, publications, loans, and research projects. Files on artists may concern purchases of the artist's work, exhibitions or publications concerning the artist, and/or may contain Collection correspondence with the artist. Folders found outside of this run fitting into this framework were added to it. The last 15 folders comprise Collection correspondence. This material documents the generosity with which the Silverman Collection opened itself to researchers, as well as the warm relationships Hendricks and Silverman maintained with artists, scholars, and many others.
    - "484 Greenwich st. New York, NY Storage Space", undated; Photographs. (Box 197, Folder VII.A.1)
    - "488 Greenwich st. New York, NY Studio", 1987; Photographs; building plans. (Box 197, Folder VII.A.2)
    - "Harry N. Abrams, Inc.", 1985-1987; Concerns Fluxus Codex. (Box 197, Folder VII.A.3)
    - "Harry N. Abrams, Inc.", 1985-1987; Concerns Fluxus Codex. (Box 197, Folder VII.A.4)
    - "Harry N. Abrams, Inc.", 1987-1988; Concerns Fluxus Codex. (Box 197, Folder VII.A.5)
    - "Harry N. Abrams, Inc.", 1986-1988; Concerns Fluxus Codex. (Box 197, Folder VII.A.6)
    - "Vito Acconci", 1982-1984 (Box 197, Folder VII.A.7)
    - "AG Gallery", undated (Box 197, Folder VII.A.8)
    - "Juan J. Agius", 1993-1994; Regards purchases from Livres et Multiples, Geneva. (Box 197, Folder VII.A.9)
    - Kuniharu Akiyama, 1983, 1996; Copies of correspondence from Hendricks to Kuniharu Akiyama. (Box 197, Folder VII.A.10)
    - "Albrecht d.", 1984, 1993-1995 (Box 197, Folder VII.A.11)
    - "Bruce Altshuler", 1988, 1991 (Box 197, Folder VII.A.12)
    - "Salvatore Alva Gallery", 1990-1991 (Box 197, Folder VII.A.13)
    - "Salvatore Alva Gallery", 1990-1991 (Box 197, Folder VII.A.14)
    - "and / or", 1985-1987; Regards purchase of negatives from 1977 Fluxfest. (Box 197, Folder VII.A.15)
    - "Eric Anderisch", 1992-1994 (Box 197, Folder VII.A.16)
    - "Aaagard Andersen", 1985, 1993 (Box 197, Folder VII.A.17)
    - "Eric Andersen", 1994-1996 (Box 197, Folder VII.A.18)
    - "Eric Andersen", 1996-1998 (Box 197, Folder VII.A.19)
    - "Eric Andersen", 1983-1995 (Box 197, Folder VII.A.20)
    - "Simon Andersen", 1983-1992 (Box 198, Folder VII.A.21)
    - "Barbara and Nancy Anello", 1986 (Box 198, Folder VII.A.22)
    - "Anonymous", undated; Photographs of works in collection. (Box 198, Folder VII.A.23)
    - "Anthology Film Archives", 1989, 1996 (Box 198, Folder VII.A.24)
    - "Anthology Film Archives", 1986 (Box 198, Folder VII.A.25)
    - "John Applefield", 1994-1996 (Box 198, Folder VII.A.26)
    - Appraisal of the collection, undated; Listed by inventory number. 21 pages. (Box 198, Folder VII.A.27)
    - "Appropriation Art", 1998; Newsclipping. (Box 198, Folder VII.A.28)
    - "Archive Shelves for Storage Boxes", undated; Regards Silverman Collection shelves designed by Larry Miller and built by Tehching Hsieh. (Box 198, Folder VII.A.29)
    - "Archives", 1995; Newsclipping. (Box 198, Folder VII.A.30)
    - "ARLIS 1989" (Box 198, Folder VII.A.31)
    - "Arman", 1984-1985; Regards purchase of work. (Box 198, Folder VII.A.32)
    - "John Armleder", undated (Box 198, Folder VII.A.33)
    - "Liz Armstrong", 1989-1994 (Box 198, Folder VII.A.34)
    - "Art for the World", 1997 (Box 198, Folder VII.A.35)
    - "Art Library Journal", 1983-1984; Regards Hendricks article, "Aspects of Fluxus from The Gilbert and Lila Silverman Collection." Art Libraries Journal, vol 8, no. 3 (Autumn 1983). (Box 198, Folder VII.A.36)
    - "Art Library Journal", 1983-1984; Regards Hendricks article, "Aspects of Fluxus from The Gilbert and Lila Silverman Collection." Art Libraries Journal, vol 8, no. 3 (Autumn 1983). (Box 198, Folder VII.A.37)
    - "Art Metropole", 1983-1997 (Box 198, Folder VII.A.38)
    - "Artforum", 1984-1988 (Box 198, Folder VII.A.39)
    - "Arthouse", 1997; Regards purchases. (Box 198, Folder VII.A.40)
    - "Artists' bios", undated (Box 198, Folder VII.A.41)
    - "Artons", 1985 (Box 198, Folder VII.A.42)
    - "Artpack", 1985; Regards move of collection from New York to Detroit. (Box 198, Folder VII.A.43)
    - "Artpool", 1993-1995 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.44)
    - "Artrain", 1985 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.45)
    - "Arts Coalition for Freedom of Expression", 1990 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.46)
    - "Arts Magazine", 1988-1989 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.47)
    - "Artscribe", 1989 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.48)
    - "Association Art-Terre", 1989-1994 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.49)
    - "Betty Asher", 1989-1994 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.50)
    - "Maeva Aubert", 1995 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.51)
    - "Auckland City Art Gallery", 1984-1985 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.52)
    - "Auction Prices - Fluxus Works", 1988 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.53)
    - "Walter Aurich", 1989 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.54)
    - "Awards", 1988 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.55)
    - "Ay-O", 1976-1988 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.56)
    - "Ay-O", undated; Photographs of works in collection. (Box 199, Folder VII.A.57)
    - Ay-O, 1983; ALS Ay-O - Hendricks (3/28/1983); copy of response.; Note: for audio tape sent by Ay-O with this letter, see IX.C.20. (Box 199, Folder VII.A.58)
    - "A-Z Art Framing", 1998 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.59)
    - "Mats B.", 1984-1993 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.60)
    - "Backworks", 1996 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.61)
    - "Inge Baecker", 1987-1998 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.62)
    - "Eliza Baer", 1996 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.63)
    - "Dorte Baggenaes", 1991 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.64)
    - "John Baldessari", 1986; Newsclipping. (Box 199, Folder VII.A.65)
    - Ball Checkers, 1987-1989 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.66)
    - "Klaus Batz", 1994 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.67)
    - "BBC 'Fluxus' program", 1996-1997 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.68)
    - "Marianne Bech", 1995 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.69)
    - "Bell Art Gallery, Brown University", 1983-1984 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.70)
    - "Fatima Bercht", 1986 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.71)
    - "Carol Berg", 1991-2002 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.72)
    - "Michael Berger", 2007 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.73)
    - "Michael and Ute Berger", 1989-1996 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.74)
    - "Tobias Berger", 1989-1997 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.75)
    - "Jeff Berner", 1980-1993 (Box 199, Folder VII.A.76)
    - "Jeff Berner", 1989-1992 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.77)
    - "Jeff Berner", 1989-1994 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.78)
    - "Joseph Beuys", 1981-1991 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.79)
    - "Bibliography - Fluxus", undated (Box 200, Folder VII.A.80)
    - Bibliography - Fluxus, undated (Box 200, Folder VII.A.81)
    - "Guy Bleus", 2000 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.82)
    - "Ren and Ursula Block", 1983-1995 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.83)
    - "Ren and Ursula Block", 1992 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.84)
    - "Ina Blom", 1991-1995 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.85)
    - "Blum Art Institute, Bard College", 1985 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.86)
    - "Boca Raton Museum", 1991 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.87)
    - "Bologna Fluxus Show", 1978; Photographs by Geoffrey Hendricks. (Box 200, Folder VII.A.88)
    - "Peder Bonnier", undated (Box 200, Folder VII.A.89)
    - "Bound and Unbound", 1989-1991 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.90)
    - "Don Boyd", 1987-1995 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.91)
    - "George Brecht", 1975-1985 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.92)
    - "George Brecht", 1976-1989 (Box 200, Folder VII.A.93)
    - "George Brecht", undated; Photographs of works in collection. (Box 200, Folder VII.A.94)
    - George Brecht - Notebooks, 2003-2004 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.95)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.96)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.97)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.98)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.99)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.100)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.101)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.102)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.103)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.104)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 201, Folder VII.A.105)
    - George Brecht - Photographs of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.106)
    - George Brecht - Transparencies of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.107)
    - George Brecht - Transparencies of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.108)
    - George Brecht - Transparencies of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.109)
    - George Brecht - Transparencies of works in the collection, 2005 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.110)
    - "Anne Brenner", 1989 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.111)
    - "Vicky Breslin", 1984 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.112)
    - "Eli Broad Foundation", 1994 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.113)
    - Marcel Broodthaers, undated; Photographs of works in collection. (Box 202, Folder VII.A.114)
    - "Rosemary Brooks", 1984 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.115)
    - "Bob Brown (estate of Jean Brown)", 1994 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.116)
    - "Earle Brown", 1984 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.117)
    - "Jean Brown Archive", 1984-1985 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.118)
    - "Jean Brown Archive", 1983-1991 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.119)
    - "Robert Delford Brown", 1995 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.120)
    - "John Brumfield", 1983 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.121)
    - "Barry Bryant", 1997 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.122)
    - Brian Buczak, undated; Photographs of works in collection. (Box 202, Folder VII.A.123)
    - "Brian Buczak", 1987 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.124)
    - "Bobby Buecker", 1983-1985 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.125)
    - "Charlton Burch", 1982-1985 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.126)
    - "Sylvano Bussotti", 1997 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.127)
    - "Joseph Byrd", undated (Box 202, Folder VII.A.128)
    - C. K. & L. Hardware, 2004; News clipping about Canal st. supply store (New York Times, 8/31/2004). (Box 202, Folder VII.A.129)
    - "John Cage", undated (Box 202, Folder VII.A.130)
    - Alexander Calder, undated (Box 202, Folder VII.A.131)
    - "John Cale", 1989-1993 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.132)
    - "Vincent Carducci", 1989 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.133)
    - "Sean Carillo", 1997 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.134)
    - "Arthur Caspari", undated (Box 202, Folder VII.A.135)
    - "Leo Castelli Gallery", 1985 (Box 202, Folder VII.A.136)
    - "Cataloging Systems", 1986 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.137)
    - Cataloging/Museum Registration Methods/Policy of Use, 1987-1988; Concerns archival storage boxes. (Box 203, Folder VII.A.138)
    - Cataloging/Museum Registration Methods/Policy of Use, 1983-1987; Concerns archival storage. (Box 203, Folder VII.A.139)
    - Cataloging/Museum Registration Methods/Policy of Use, 1987; "Larry Miller's plans for office." (Box 203, Folder VII.A.140)
    - Cataloging/Museum Registration Methods/Policy of Use, 1987; "Bookcases - Coosje's system used in Detroit." (Box 203, Folder VII.A.141)
    - Cataloging/Museum Registration Methods/Policy of Use, 1991-1994 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.142)
    - Cataloging/Museum Registration Methods/Policy of Use, 1991; "Policies of uses of archival materials." (Box 203, Folder VII.A.143)
    - Cataloging/Museum Registration Methods/Policy of Use, 1987; "Jean Brown storage system" and "Archive Sohm storage system." (Box 203, Folder VII.A.144)
    - Cataloging/Museum Registration Methods/Policy of Use, 1989; "Art Networks and Information Systems." (Box 203, Folder VII.A.145)
    - Cataloging/Museum Registration Methods/Policy of Use, 1991; "Cataloging Systems." (Box 203, Folder VII.A.146)
    - Cataloging/Museum Registration Methods/Policy of Use, 1983; "Rifkind Foundation." (Box 203, Folder VII.A.147)
    - "Center for Contemporary Arts, Warsaw", 1990 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.148)
    - "Centre de la Vieille Charite, Marseille", 1993 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.149)
    - "Centre Georges Pompidou", 1986, 1995 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.150)
    - "Centre Georges Pompidou", 2005; Concerns No Smoking by George Brecht. (Box 203, Folder VII.A.151)
    - "Henry Chalfant", 1985 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.152)
    - "Michael R. Chalian", 1982 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.153)
    - "Giuseppe Chiari", 1980-1983 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.154)
    - "Giuseppe Chiari", 1983-1989 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.155)
    - "Giuseppe Chiari", undated; Photographs of works in collection. (Box 203, Folder VII.A.156)
    - "Rosanna Chiessi", 1984 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.157)
    - "Henri Chopin", 1989 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.158)
    - "Charlotte Christiansen", 1985 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.159)
    - "Henning Christiansen", 1985-1992 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.160)
    - "Henning Christiansen", 1987-1991 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.161)
    - "Christo", 1980-1995 (Box 203, Folder VII.A.162)
    - "Jack Coke's Farmer's Co-op", undated; Photograph of work in collection. (Box 204, Folder VII.A.163)
    - "Colette", 1998 (Box 204, Folder VII.A.164)
    - "Collection Management", 1995 (Box 204, Folder VII.A.165)
    - "Complaints - Various", 1993 (Box 204, Folder VII.A.166)
    - "Conservation", 1984-1985, 1996 (Box 204, Folder VII.A.167)
    - Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius, 1995, 2007-2008, undated (Box 204, Folder VII.A.168)
    - Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius (Box 204, Folder VII.A.169)
    - "Contempory Art Center, Lithuania", 1994-1996 (Box 204, Folder VII.A.170)
    - "Contempory Arts Museum, Houston", 1984 (Box 204, Folder VII.A.171)
    - "William Copley", 1989 (Box 204, Folder VII.A.172)
    - "Copyrights", 1987, 1995 (Box 204, Folder VII.A.173)
    - "Philip Corner", 1997-1999; Ephemera. (Box 204, Folder VII.A.174)